<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CI/CD on Obi Ifediba</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/ci/cd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CI/CD on Obi Ifediba</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Obi Ifediba</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/ci/cd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hamburger besides wisp something annually my</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/hamburger-besides-wisp-something-annually-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/hamburger-besides-wisp-something-annually-my/</guid>
      <description>Note This is a randomly generated note for demonstrating the content graph feature. Them Einsteinian those yearly these all nevertheless want where are helpless sedge usually for work his previously either there. None cluster Russian those when peace office you these child few had whose up for are regiment his that. Stand year news sometimes your those those that near several firstly your sit.&#xA;When over early him that hers Finnish still conditioner girl towards that open meanwhile then vanish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alone why dynasty embarrassed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/alone-why-dynasty-embarrassed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/alone-why-dynasty-embarrassed/</guid>
      <description>Note This is a randomly generated note for demonstrating the content graph feature. Either South weekly ourselves hat her so rather begin heavy himself Indonesian in straightaway for wood smell. Were thoughtful almost even i.e. why from eventually staff wait collection look anyone whoever secondly i.e. awfully. Clumsy fun outside was blushing brightly since precious much recently since have thoroughly as dazzle how frail. This neither oil huge himself country sharply it than these other lately your for to host who.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
